[Music]
No
pillow, I don't want any more food. [Music] You're really
fat.  Yes, you are right, do something.
Hey go and wash the clothes,
so go and see quickly my store
[Music]
yikes yikes all these uneducated fools in
line [Music] who is abusing the water tank
[Music]
or are we talking about water, water is precious, water is precious, water is precious, the cave is
smoking, the cave is sweeping, everyone needs water, I don't
say no, I am a fool, I am a
scholar, I have no intellect, mother-in-law, I am a
plus two fail, I will not work, I am an
ordinary person, pond, house, village,
wash clothes, cow, cow, wash clothes, wash clothes, I don't
say water, go and wash clothes,
see, wash clothes with tube water, don't get any disease, wash clothes with pond water,
your
body is bad, you said, touch the cup, if you don't touch it, you will be sick, look, touch the pot, if you touch it, you will be sick, if you touch it, you will be sick,
yes, if you touch the pot, you will
not feel any pain, you said,
today but for three years, who is Thakur, if you touch it, it will be
empty  Pachi look I have not touched you, she said where have you touched you enter,
you are a fool, you are a drug addict,
you go to whose house have you touched what to do, line Nathla
's motor Nathla, this car, water, you have touched,
wash all the clothes, you
Nathla,
Baba Baba, go,
uncle Dhani, what do you do, I
too should go first, touch it
[screaming] Dango's pencil is cut, you are crying, you are telling me [crying
] O Aapa Shanti,
what will happen to me
[music] [crying]
[
laughter]
tell me, oh lie, lie,
water, wash, wash the
clothes, wash them,
say it
[laughter]
wash it, brother, wash it, you are my
aunt
[music], go and do the
work
[crying]
[crying] what do you
see,
Baba,
one
[crying]
no, what do you do
[music],
shut up, father, shut up, magic
slippers
[crying  [voice]
[ __ ]
up ko drishti pau
[laughter]
Shut up baba
shut up
[crying voice] I did
n't even understand him
[laughter] You will get
sick from money she said
[crying voice]
[crying voice
]
Hey brother what's my brother's life
[music]
Hey Pund
Thakurani mother
give me drishti let's
take it to the doctor doctor
give me the full test medicine
medicine
hey
pet
re
drishti party should
start
[music] what do you do
you have done
violence to the innocent [music] kill me don't kill me
animal beat me
fool hawk p
look at the dogs don't
waste time
mother also brother whose life is saved today Kali Maa j
dehri re feed me chhu khani turn around
[music]
p samo who po look what
fill me look and feed me
check the diaper with water and wash the stomach [crying voice]
you should change the diaper
drishti pakesi
brother ko temple so give me the money give me the good
money  Leave the door and do
not put the complete bandh, I have not put the money in the
whole night,
my condition is good, take the money, you are right, fool,
my condition is good [laughter]
[crying sound]
you forgive me, Thakur, king, I have to
go to the doctor, I am suffering, quickly,
quickly,
sit on the scooter, go to the doctor [crying sound]
Banshi [music] brother, you have to take five people with you, take
TV, mobile, national and international news, I am still getting
water,
now I will go to the king and the minister [laughter]
of Sundar,
Chamunda, Guru, brother,
brother, okay,
who is saying this, it is good, I am looking at Chandi, Chandi, I am
climbing on your chest,
really
Bhaki, oh oh oh oh oh oh,
someone, oh oh
[music]
we